[{"teacherID":"68aa2143-d719-4b26-9b49-261874d5b4c8","comments":[{"date":"2023-04-01","replys":[{"date":"2023-04-01","replys":[],"id":"c5b6bf3c-4302-4d73-bc77-c2cfcde2c50a","userID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","content":"is cool"}],"id":"ac876ebd-3f3d-42ac-a76e-627b6403a8e8","userID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","content":"bob jones"},{"date":"2023-04-01","replys":[],"id":"384bbae7-a66e-4885-b498-69ba48231d7d","userID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","content":"he is not very cool"}],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"What goes in the () in the DOM call?","id":"61b35412-e44d-4f1a-8d7b-f815da04df3e","choices":["An element's ID","An elephant","An src tag","An h1 tag"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"Test your knowledge","id":"4f6ecc8e-93c5-4603-962f-28b391612ceb","title":"JavaScript DOM"},"comments":[],"description":"Use JavaScript DOM to access HTML elements","id":"cc9fd7b6-c607-49bd-85c9-01c1ff189f97","title":"Access Elements","lessons":[{"comments":[{"date":"2023-04-01","replys":[{"date":"2023-04-01","replys":[],"id":"a1efbcf7-83ed-4ba1-a7e7-0c219d22b5f9","userID":"fbf8ecae-a7c0-4ab9-9a0a-ac1f8f3b764d","content":"No it's not"}],"id":"c26abd8b-9a85-4db9-8ff3-e4316d70f03e","userID":"fbf8ecae-a7c0-4ab9-9a0a-ac1f8f3b764d","content":"This class is fun"}],"id":"dd18c778-d9cb-44d2-b289-18a7458700da","title":"Get Element By Id","content":"If you have an HTML element with an id, then you can use JavaScript DOM to access it.\n\nThe script is:\n\ndocument.getElementById(\"<<id>>\").MODIFIER"}]}],"description":"Learn about Document Object Model","students":[],"language":"JAVASCRIPT","id":"4bc8473a-fbd6-4824-933d-ce7cea69e845","title":"JavaScript DOM"},{"teacherID":"68aa2143-d719-4b26-9b49-261874d5b4c8","comments":[],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"1","id":"959825ef-efdd-4bfe-bcca-743dbe6ce1a4","choices":["1","1","1","1"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"1","id":"bdb50674-19de-4acc-856e-467272a872bf","title":"1"},"comments":[],"description":"1","id":"21f86a3d-ae76-4d8c-8e88-1998443b2a54","title":"1","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"5289fb21-245e-4038-89e9-e744826a315f","title":"1","content":"1"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"2","id":"fdad33ff-8be9-4b2b-a4eb-3e9a1a22355b","choices":["2","2","2","2"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"2","id":"395eb9fd-a0a4-4429-b8e5-89f575df6ebf","title":"2"},"comments":[],"description":"2","id":"17e4db43-4fbf-4ab1-b525-7969fc6e651d","title":"2","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"6482e1c3-ebc4-4a62-af7d-bf078be69619","title":"2","content":"2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"3","id":"700449db-ff75-422e-ab22-baff8a0e995d","choices":["3","3","3","3"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"3","id":"1dfc19d3-bd9c-490a-aadc-37cffe6179ab","title":"3"},"comments":[],"description":"3","id":"dd2d1f30-02f6-45a1-a030-e8f31bde0f24","title":"3","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"ba57aed7-011a-4098-9317-6673711dd41e","title":"3","content":"3"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"4","id":"f6fd968e-4e4a-4ea1-8379-1f08c7a6d676","choices":["4","4","4","4"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"4","id":"31c32a8e-055e-4168-ab77-c34aee82d21e","title":"4"},"comments":[],"description":"4","id":"6db25d4c-8f37-4188-b221-a613aaade216","title":"4","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"36c6b18a-fe21-4ffc-a1f0-15387042f4ee","title":"4","content":"4"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"5","id":"9853e9f1-33f6-449f-9f51-3ad4c6c90549","choices":["5","5","5","5"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"5","id":"fda1081f-a177-4405-a76f-c5bc630b7210","title":"5"},"comments":[],"description":"5","id":"15f7d728-5ca0-4db4-a7fa-dccb48023fe0","title":"5","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"78019f2b-6dd4-4b9e-ae19-3b3ffa7d5974","title":"5","content":"5"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"6","id":"6beb8830-e4d4-4709-a360-f5dfb1285c99","choices":["6","6","6","6"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"6","id":"5a152c2f-140b-407e-9232-b8a540df8365","title":"6"},"comments":[],"description":"6","id":"4f3f8aa0-59cb-4996-ba0a-b59b38424307","title":"6","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"dd4c098a-567b-41aa-a48d-7a1e13bf93c4","title":"6","content":"6"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"7","id":"a8eb0fdc-4fb3-44fc-8a6b-a0aa9c8258c4","choices":["7","7","7","7"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"7","id":"e3cc3060-5f51-4c2a-b0a3-63871e31cef7","title":"7"},"comments":[],"description":"7","id":"40e668f7-01aa-4439-adca-ef578f53aa4d","title":"7","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"8ccabe46-34b3-48b6-9718-64b837f3696d","title":"7","content":"7"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"8","id":"7cf096ff-32de-4287-adf9-d5817bee0222","choices":["8","8","8","8"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"8","id":"24cfc595-3632-4dac-8197-bec2f53f3e5a","title":"8"},"comments":[],"description":"8","id":"e910d230-180c-4524-9de2-957f00e5f280","title":"8","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"730ba044-7571-405f-8f82-01a93d5efe38","title":"8","content":"8"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"9","id":"ef2060c3-f4b1-4e5d-8451-db0e6185ba7b","choices":["9","9","9","9"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"9","id":"46148a56-b00c-45e8-807a-f041d07dc60a","title":"9"},"comments":[],"description":"9","id":"738e1a3c-e3e1-48d7-ae48-99572b5459d9","title":"9","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"7504bf91-d06d-4ff0-9f53-e54e492a7196","title":"9","content":"9"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"t","id":"2c284772-a8d8-44a1-bb3b-4560c62ed3c8","choices":["t","t","t","t"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"t","id":"917beb7b-b4d9-4d56-b434-5b84ea23ce0d","title":"t"},"comments":[],"description":"t","id":"fe0bfa95-8163-4a20-b9b0-5e9d91c4b2bb","title":"t","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"2fe6b915-9cd1-453d-8b08-2f402e0d4843","title":"t","content":"t"}]}],"description":"t","students":[],"language":"PYTHON","id":"72437f34-c8ff-4678-98d9-caaf6470a8ea","title":"t"},{"teacherID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","comments":[],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[],"description":"none","id":"00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000","title":"none"},"comments":[],"description":"t","id":"f2589bee-deeb-4abc-80c7-6365dd6b7432","title":"t","lessons":[]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"t","id":"3fa36cdf-b58f-4457-b053-de97aab3e8b4","choices":["t","t","t","t"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"t","id":"3fa38c97-00e2-4d74-9aa6-74264478eefd","title":"t"},"comments":[],"description":"sdf","id":"2bc0b9f1-1471-42a6-b97e-4b9fd46baf67","title":"pee","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"17494ec5-9b46-4ad1-aa3e-9c32681d54b8","title":"t","content":"t"}]}],"description":"t","students":[],"language":"CSHARP","id":"398cbf81-34f5-45a9-8e09-f3904b5ea2f5","title":"t"},{"teacherID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","comments":[],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"bob","id":"1955dc69-f9ea-4221-9614-b472520371b9","choices":["l","l","l","l"],"correctAnswerIndex":0},{"question":"bob","id":"107a9d85-962b-4772-9ad7-0f25ea7bd756","choices":["jones","i","i","i"],"correctAnswerIndex":0},{"question":"e","id":"4b2261a4-9f09-479b-bf73-49ac9b32aa48","choices":["e","e","e","e"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"1","id":"c37d1e2d-71fd-4b29-8b1a-376e4d1ac223","title":"test quiz"},"comments":[],"description":"q","id":"715a6d55-9b7f-4559-9768-698350c19b3a","title":"qq","lessons":[]}],"description":"q","students":[],"language":"CSHARP","id":"2713561b-cf0f-4e1c-b4c6-78a67a8c9480","title":"q"},{"teacherID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","comments":[],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"r","id":"b64ce1cc-47cd-43ce-b717-637b605636f6","choices":["r","r","r","r"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"e","id":"09de4130-2498-483f-a907-d70273c2da62","title":"e"},"comments":[],"description":"e","id":"f6ecce51-13ca-4762-85d9-830406274f21","title":"e","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"d848006a-471e-4823-b13b-e632358ab8e4","title":"e","content":"e"}]}],"description":"e","students":[],"language":"CSHARP","id":"f4406d90-c246-4443-84cb-81bc26794973","title":"e"},{"teacherID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","comments":[],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"l","id":"951dceb7-6518-44f4-bcaf-6cc76eb61799","choices":["l","l","l","l"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"l","id":"f6f7e195-57d7-4d12-b859-1153c855b252","title":"l"},"comments":[],"description":"l","id":"29bcbcaf-9541-4669-bb4e-6c3633694c59","title":"l","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"62f172fe-72b9-43a3-a9a0-b618ca8d189e","title":"l","content":"l"}]}],"description":"l","students":[],"language":"CSHARP","id":"e5f36e55-a699-47d2-af46-3e979d230222","title":"l"},{"teacherID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","comments":[],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"l","id":"67228c36-01b6-4b19-9a9c-89ea335b34a7","choices":["ll","l","l","l"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"l","id":"cae8032f-4127-4cf5-bb8b-2c182d4b26da","title":"l"},"comments":[],"description":"l","id":"c664aaf7-a2a6-4fcd-9ce2-cfb7220ac3eb","title":"l","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"2293f47b-df7f-45f8-a724-e33b734f367f","title":"l","content":"l"}]}],"description":"l","students":[],"language":"CSHARP","id":"d5b06121-96de-4d17-853a-e4cecd773ea9","title":"l"},{"teacherID":"d6577ddf-067a-4d1c-a4d1-c50222ae6a71","comments":[],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"l","id":"12853fde-f68c-4c42-b858-902f55b9e129","choices":["l","l","l","l"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"l","id":"c61d536d-f7ec-459c-8066-8cc6a2d9e32a","title":"l"},"comments":[],"description":"l","id":"826cb4a9-cb8d-41be-bed0-039d2acef590","title":"l","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"faeee499-9aac-47b3-a2f5-76a8daa8a174","title":"l","content":"l"}]}],"description":"l","students":[],"language":"CSHARP","id":"42c54327-e61c-46a4-83a6-1fdf5416888a","title":"l"},{"teacherID":"fbf8ecae-a7c0-4ab9-9a0a-ac1f8f3b764d","comments":[],"reviews":[],"topics":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"l","id":"7ff70980-3c3c-4e9f-928d-36698ace1592","choices":["l","l","l","l"],"correctAnswerIndex":0}],"description":"t","id":"e10f432f-1f35-4e59-96bc-9274d9a1bbf9","title":"test"},"comments":[],"description":"AP","id":"a9d1059f-5b10-45dc-b786-c80eff7e69a4","title":"Accounts Payable","lessons":[{"comments":[],"id":"32754ce9-3825-4c85-91cf-c0db2f1e375b","title":"e","content":"e"}]}],"description":"Coding for finance","students":[{"studentID":"0c9c939a-c580-4318-842c-055aa74ff4b9","grades":[{"quizID":"e10f432f-1f35-4e59-96bc-9274d9a1bbf9","id":"318e9322-0486-4438-8556-8b0ffc709bdf","gradePercentage":100.0}]}],"language":"JAVA","id":"bff0bef1-9cb1-4023-b765-33bd670f94d4","title":"Finance 101"}]